<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks | SUES</title>
    <link>https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:51:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://IJLIPC.github.io/images/icon_hu70174535b56a425300a2f8918e6f02fa_486585_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Recent &amp; Upcoming Talks</title>
      <link>https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postgraduate</title>
      <link>https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/team/student/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:51:05 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/team/student/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Team</title>
      <link>https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/team/teachers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2020 09:51:05 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://IJLIPC.github.io/talk/team/teachers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://seee.sues.edu.cn/_upload/article/images/0d/1d/de2c977c431b8ae71376ed9751eb/88893b97-19d3-41ae-b016-1de48c65f568.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;职称&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;教授&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;research direction&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Pattern recognition, intelligent computing, video analysis&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;mailing address&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;School of Electronic and Electrical Engineering, 9th Floor, Administration Building, No.333 Longteng Road, Songjiang District, Shanghai&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Postal code&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;201620&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;contact number&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;67791013&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;E-mail&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:zjfang@gmail.com&#34;&gt;zjfang@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:zjfang@sues.edu.cn&#34;&gt;zjfang@sues.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Zhijun Fang&lt;/strong&gt;，Male, born in Poyang, Jiangxi, is currently the Dean of the School of Electrical and Electronic Engineering, Shanghai University of Engineering and Technology. Born in September 1971, member of the Communist Party of China. Doctor of Engineering, Shanghai Jiaotong University. Senior member of China Computer Society, IEEE senior member, member of Multimedia Technology Committee of China Computer Society, executive director of China Management Science and Engineering Society, director of National Basic Computer Education Research Association.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 2007, he was selected as the training target of the first &amp;ldquo;Jiangxi Provincial Young Scientist (Jinggang Star)&amp;rdquo; and the young and middle-aged academic leader in Jiangxi universities. In 2008, he was selected as the &amp;ldquo;Top Ten Outstanding Young People&amp;rdquo; of Jiangxi University of Finance and Economics and one of the hundreds of talented candidates in Jiangxi Province. In 2011, he was elected as the &amp;ldquo;Top Ten IT&amp;rdquo; youth in Jiangxi Province. In 2012, he was selected as the leading talent of Jiangxi Province&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Gan Po 555 Project&amp;rdquo;. In 2013, he was selected as the first batch of public security video surveillance technical personnel of the Ministry of Public Security (a total of 93 nationwide), and the academic and technical leader of major disciplines in Jiangxi Province. In 2015, he was selected as the leading talent in Jiangxi University of Finance and Economics&amp;rsquo; &amp;ldquo;Hundred Talents Program&amp;rdquo;. In 2011, he was appointed as the Dean of the School of Information Management of Jiangxi University of Finance and Economics, and in 2013, he was hired as a doctoral supervisor of Management Science and Engineering (Service Computing) of Jiangxi University of Finance and Economics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He is also the director of Jiangxi Key Laboratory of Digital Media, executive deputy director of Jiangxi E-commerce Engineering Technology Research Center, and executive deputy director of Jiangxi Public Security Video Technology Research Center.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He has presided over the completion of key projects of the National Development and Reform Commission, the National Natural Science Foundation of China, the Ministry of Public Security Application Innovation Program, the Jiangxi Provincial Foreign Science and Technology Cooperation Project, the Jiangxi Provincial Higher School Science and Technology Landing Project, and other projects. Chairman or co-chair of the committee.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://seee.sues.edu.cn/_upload/article/images/7e/48/805a5c274f3e93920142620103f9/9143d41d-7ceb-45f2-a1be-07d55d380004.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;img&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;职称&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;副教授&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;research direction&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Artificial intelligence, machine learning, image processing, pattern recognition&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;mailing address&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Room 7718, Modern Transportation Engineering Center, Shanghai University of Engineering Technology, Songjiang District, Shanghai&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;Postal code&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;201620&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;contact number&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;021-6779-1131&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;E-mail&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&#34;center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:gaoyongbin@sues.edu.cn&#34;&gt;gaoyongbin@sues.edu.cn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Yongbin Gao&lt;/strong&gt;，Shanghai Chenguang Optical, who has received public funding from the National Fund Committee since 2013, is pursuing a doctorate at Jeonbuk National University in South Korea. Published more than 40 papers, including IEEE Transaction on Image Processing, Information Sciences, Pattern Recognition Letters, Signal Processing: Image Communication, ICME and other well-known SCI retrieval papers/top conferences, and EI retrieval 5 papers. After returning to China in 2017, he joined the School of Electronic and Electrical Engineering of Shanghai University of Engineering and Technology, presided over 4 national youth fund projects/provincial and ministerial projects, and participated in key projects of the National Fund Committee and key projects of the Shanghai Science and Technology Commission as the main technical person in charge. In 2019, he won the second prize of Shanghai Science and Technology Progress Award (ranked 3rd).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At the same time, actively promote the cooperation of industry, university and research institute, with COMAC Shanghai Aircraft Manufacturing Co., Ltd., Shanghai Zhenhua Heavy Industry Group, Shanghai Palm Teng Intelligent Technology Co., Ltd. (technical consultant), Shanghai Youluoke Electronic Technology Co., Ltd., Shanghai Zhongshan Hospital, Shanghai Changzheng Hospital, Fudan University Affiliated Eye, Ear, Nose and Throat Hospital, etc. carry out in-depth industry-university-research cooperation. They are mainly responsible for 5 horizontal topics. Research areas include: UAV positioning and navigation, SLAM technology, 3D visual analysis, face recognition, palm vein recognition , Vehicle model recognition, multi-target recognition and tracking, behavior recognition, medical image-assisted diagnosis (CTA analysis of coronary heart disease and gastric cancer).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
